Today, Rei Inoue and Sakura Ishiyama from Juice Juice came to TV Arichi!
I'm Rei Inoue and Sakura Ishiyama from Juice Juice. This is Rei Inoue. I'm Sakura Ishiyama. Please give me a warm welcome.
Today, I would like to ask you a lot about your new song.
The song has been getting a lot of attention on youtube and has already had a lot of views.
First of all, what kind of song is "Pride Bride"?
I think there are many people who get the first impression that "Pride Bride" is very cool.
I think there are a lot of people who get the first impression that Pride Bride is very cool, and the way the members sing is also very vigorous and powerful, but I think it's really a song about a girl who can't be honest.
I'm a girl who can't really be honest, and that's why I'm so strong and forceful.
I think it's an interesting song that is interpreted in different ways by different people.
I think it is a song that can be interpreted in different ways depending on the feelings of the listeners.
I thought the cool expressions on everyone's faces were really nice.
But I think the singer's true feelings behind the cool expressions are also included in the song.
Yes, that's right.
I sing a lot when I release a new song.
But we don't talk so much about how we feel about the song.
It's rather natural for Juice members to sing their solos the way they want to.
It's a matter of course that Juice sings their solos the way they want.
If it's unison or something like that, we'll talk about it.
But all the songs are interpreted by each of us.
Sometimes we talk about how great this singer is.
Heh...
But the fashionable JuiceJuice worldview is always there.
I think it's always there.
Thank you very much.
I thought the music video was really wonderful.
Were there any scenes that were difficult or enjoyable that you remember?
During the lip scene, you don't sing the lyrics, you just touch your lips.
Lip de-hap.
You had a great voice.
What? Like...
He said, "I'm going to upload it," and I said, "I'm going to upload it.
And then they said, "We're going to upload it, but you're going to have to mess with your lips.
I was like, "What? I had a lot of trouble with that.
Heh.Heh.
It's not like they told me in advance that they were going to do that, but they just said, "We're going to do it right there and then.
Yes, I was told that.
They told me that.
You're lying!
Insufficient confirmation.
But it's difficult, isn't it?
It's hard to know how to prepare when you're told in advance that you're only going to upload your lips.
But I made my lip color darker than usual and made it more glossy.
I went for the "do-happ" look, but the movement of the lips is so delicate and difficult.
The movement of the lips is very delicate, so it's difficult to do.
But you can't just sing along...
I see.
I got a big grin on my face the moment the cut was made.
That's right.
That scene is a highlight.
Yes, by all means.
Hee...
Party Flushing is another song that conveys a refreshing and energetic summery feeling.
What do you think is attractive about this song?
Well, when I first heard it, I thought it was very Tatsuro Yamashita in a good way.
I thought it was a Tatsuro Yamashita song in a good way, but I wanted to make it Juice Juice's style.
I had to make it sound like Juice Juice, but I also had to make it sound like Tatsuro Yamashita.
But I had to sing it with respect for Tatsuro Yamashita.
I didn't know what to do anymore.
I was imagining what the song would be like if it was sung by Juice Juice's predecessors in the past or by the predecessors of today.
But when the soundtrack itself came out, I was really surprised at how summery it was.
I was really surprised at how summery it was when the soundtrack itself was created.
Ishihara-san's smile was so beautiful!
Thank you very much!
The music video was full of everyone's happy feeling, wasn't it?
Yes, there were some scenes with a kind of filter.
And there was also a scene with fireworks at the end.There was also a scene with fireworks at the end.
I didn't even know who the members were until it was finished.
It's my favorite music video.
I was also wondering about the part of "Let's Make" where you are making something.
What kind of choreography is that?
He's mixing something.
Is he mixing it up? It's so mixed up.
What's he mixing?
We know it's mixing something.
The teacher also assumed that he was mixing it, and he put a lot of emphasis on how many times it was spun.
Juice?
By hand?
Like spinning ice.
Well, he's holding the juice, so he does it.
That's just my imagination.
I see.
I was thinking of copying you at a live performance.
I was wondering what's going on with your hand, and then I checked some music videos.
There?
Are these chopsticks? Or is it chopsticks?
He showed me in great detail.
I don't know.
But the choreography was so catchy that I was really looking forward to seeing it live.
Please come and see it!
Thank you very much.
I've come up with 10 questions I'd like to ask you both, so I'll just answer one question at a time.
I'd like you to answer them intuitively, one question and one answer at a time.
What are you looking forward to in Nagoya?
Nagoya and Kochi
What do you like about JuiceJuice?
The freedom.
I want you to see me like this in our new song "Pride Bride
I am
I wonder if I'm like this.I guess.
What kind of person is Ms. Ishiyama from your point of view?
A beautiful woman with a funny look.
What has changed since the new member, Mifu Kawashima joined the group?
Well, Sakuringo became my senior.
What do you pay special attention to in your make-up?
A sense of blood color.
What would you like to shoot with a film camera?
Etto members' photo books
What is the source of your eye power?
Dignity, I guess.
If you could have one wish come true, what would it be?
Wow, I wish to fly!
What is your personal goal for the upcoming 6K summer tour?
I'm going to make the audience really excited.
Thank you very much.
Yes, you are on your way.
What kind of person is Mr. Ishiyama from your point of view?
Yes, she is.
I told you she's a strange beauty.
But she's always acting strange.
Always?
In pictures...
She's so pretty and beautiful.
She goes with everything.
And I think she'd look great in makeup.
But when it comes to the video
I sometimes feel that she is different from what I thought she would be
There are times when I think, "Oh, she's not what I expected.
I think she has her own view of the world.
My view of the world
Are you aware of it?
No, I am not.
But I am aware of how I look at things on a daily basis.But what is it like on a regular basis and what is
When you are in Juice-Juice and when you are in Juice-Juice
do you feel that it has not changed at all?
Yes, I think so.
I don't know if my friends are used to seeing me or what.
I don't know if my friends are used to seeing me or what, but I've never been called a strange person.
I don't usually know how I act.
I don't know how I usually behave when I'm nervous.
I've recently discovered that I have a tendency to do that.
I've only recently figured it out.
All the time.
Ever since I let my hair down.
I can tell you're nervous.
I've often wondered if you make that move when you're nervous.
You're kidding?
I'm pretty much on my own.
I was trying not to be nervous.
Did I do something wrong?
Now I know.
Next, I'd like to talk about makeup.
I thought I really liked the color of the blood.
I thought I really liked it.
Is that true?
I don't know.
I'm the type of person where the color of my lips
I'm the type of person who can change the intensity of my makeup just by the color of my lips.
No matter how light I make my eye makeup.
But if my lip color is too dark
I sometimes get told that my makeup is too dark today.
So I try to change the color of my lip color depending on my mood.
I try to change the color depending on my mood.
I never have beige.
Do you like darker color?Do you like it dark?
I do.
There's really no blood color in them.
But when I think of Inoue-san, I think of her eyes.
She changes her look depending on her makeup.
Really?
But it really makes you look more beautiful.
I'm so happy!
But Sakurachu is also amazing.
Inoue-san says I look beautiful today.
I asked her what she thought of my makeup. I asked her...
I think it's absolutely great! I think it's cute! she says.
It's all really good.
It's really good.
Thank you so much for asking me. I thought I was asking the wrong person.
It really suits you, Inoue-san.
Yes, it does.
I think so.
Not at all.
What would you like to take with a film camera?
I'd like to make a photo book of the members.
I really like film.
I like taking pictures of the members offline.
I like to take pictures of the members when they're off duty.
So I don't know what they do with the film
You don't know what they are doing until the film is developed.
I don't want to tell them to turn around and pose.
That's why I often get photographed
I don't know...
I don't know what it's like.
I don't know.
I'd like to make a book of these photos
I would like to make it into a book and offer it to everyone as merchandise.I would like to make it into a book and offer it to everyone as merchandise.
There is a demand for this kind of thing.
I'm sure there are expressions that you only show in front of Inoue-san.
When I put it on my Instagram, there are a lot of people who say, "You have a different smile.
I've had many people tell me that I have a different smile than usual, so...
Te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te.
I'm looking forward to seeing the goods.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Yes, please do.
Now, I'd like to ask Inoue-san 10 questions.
Please subscribe to our channel.
What do you enjoy in Nagoya?
Oyako-don (parent and child bowl)
What do you like about JuiceJuice?
They are free and kind.
I want you to see me like this in the new song "Pride Bride
Lip scene
What kind of person is Ms. Inoue from your point of view?
A very beautiful person with a super small face.
What has changed since the new member, Mifu Kawashima joined the group?
Hmmm...
It's not "Ichimoyo" anymore.
I feel like I've changed.
What do you pay special attention to make-up?
Mmm! Eyelashes.
You finally have a junior in JuiceJuice.
What kind of senior would you like to be?
Well, I'd like to be the one who is closest to them, like a peer.
What do you feel you have grown up in the past year?
I have relaxed a little bit.
If you could have one wish come true, what would it be?
Well, I would like to be a ninja.Well, I want to be a ninja.
What are your personal goals for the upcoming summer tour and rocking?
To gain a lot of physical strength.
And to let many people know about JuiceJuice.
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
What you like about JuiceJuice is that it is free and friendly. What do you mean by that?
When I attended my first rehearsal after joining JuiceJuice, even though I was not ready at all, they took their time to help me until I was ready,
I was very moved by their open-mindedness, and I thought they were very kind,
After spending the past year together with the members, I felt that no matter what I did, they never got angry with me,
I have spent the past year with the members, and I like the atmosphere in which no matter what I do, they don't get angry with me, or maybe that's not quite the same thing, but they let me do whatever I want.
What kind of a leader are you, Mr. Uemura?
Hmm?
Oh, why?
It's not a mistake.
Oh, I see.
He is a very cool leader who is very free but kind, and he looks out for each and every one of the members.
But you still remember how you felt when you first joined, don't you?
Yes, I remember.
I remember the angle from which Mr. Uemura was standing when he told me I'd been accepted, and the angle of the camera man in front of me.
Wow, it's so clear.
It's so clear.
That's why I cry sometimes when I remember it.
I see...
And now that Mifumi has joined, what do you mean when you say you feel like you have a motive?
Well, I think there must be some discomfort when one person joins the group.
I don't have the skills to teach her at all yet.
I don't have the skills to teach at all yet, so I'd like to have someone nearby who can be next to me, not as a motivation, but as a motivation.
Like having dinner together, or talking about trivial things that are not really work related.
I want to be someone who feels like a friend.
No, no, no.
One last thing about being a ninja...
Ninja.
Inoue-san said something unrealistic about wanting to fly in the sky, so...That Inoue-san said something quite unrealistic about wanting to fly in the sky, so
I got hung up and became a ninja.
Thank you very much.
We joke around all the time.
But I could feel how close you two are.
Thank you for this short time.
Thank you very much.
Lastly, I would like to ask you to watch this video and give a message to the audience.
As you can see, we love to joke around.
We love live performance more than anything else, so please come to our live performances.
I know there are people who can't make it to the live shows, so I hope you will come to our live shows.
We'll be updating our blogs every day, and we'd like you to support us in any way you can.
Please support us in any way you can.
We hope you will support us in any way you can.
Thank you very much.